# **JEFF SHOMALI**

info@jeffshomali.com | github.com/JeffShomali | linkedin.com/in/JeffShomali | 415-504-1135 | San Francisco, Bay Area

### **OBJECTIVE**

Full Stack Developer | Front/Back-End Web Developer | Mobile Developer

A Full Stack Developer with 5 years hands on experience in Front-End, Back-End, Web and Mobile Development. A profession in web technologies and specialize in MERN and LAMP stack, mobile development with React. Highly familiar with most recent JavaScript frameworks and libraries. In the final semester of pursuing a Bachelor of Computer Science with interest in startup, web or mobile development role.

- · Front End Web Development
- · Back End Web Development
- · Mobile Development

- · Development and Testing of Software APIs
- · Relational & Non-relational Databases
- · Server, Network & Hosting Administration

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages/Markup: NodeJS, ReactJS, React Native, Redux, JavaScript, ¡Query, HTML5, CSS3, PHP

Databases & Webservers: SQL, MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite, Nginx, Apache, Heroku, Digital Ocean

· Frameworks/Libraries: Meteor, Express, Laravel, Bootstrap, SemanticsUI, Material UI, Native Base

· CMS: WordPress, Magento, WooCommerce, Drupal, Gatsby, Jekyll

· Other Tools & Technology: NPM, Yarn, Yeoman, Webpack, Git & GitHub, Babel, Composer, RNPM

Text editors & IDEs: Sublime, Atom, Visual Studio Code, PHPStorm, WebStorm

#### **EXPERIENCE**

TutyoFull Stack Web Developer2016 - 2017PurrivacyFull Stack Web Developer (intern)2015 - 2016Freelance Developer2012 - Present

### RELEVANT PROJECTS

San Francisco Bart Application: iOS application for Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), built in React Native and Flux router. Visual Studio Code Snippet Generator: Web application to generate snippet code for VSCode. Built in React and NodeJS iOS Cryptocurrency App: iOS Cryptocurrency app to watch all coin's market data and news. Built in React Native.

Please visit my GitHub (github.com/JeffShomali) or my personal website (jeffshomali.com) for my most recent projects.

# **EDUCATION**

BS in Computer Science. Trident University - Cypress, CA - Class of Feb 2018

AS in Computer Science. Diablo Valley College - Honor Student with GPA 3.8, Pleasant Hill, CA - 2016

Certified Advanced Java Programming, Program Design and Computer Architecture from Diablo Valley College.

Certified Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree, Udacity - 2016

No work sponsorship required. References available upon request.